the search is slow, fix even the way it search, rewrite the whole search side
next fix notice so it can drop notices on everrything that is happening to the user
fix the admin pages to real data and add more page to like analysis and more to the admin section
then for the watch page add spatial sound and maybe equalizer
then add chatting with other app user
also compress or reduce the video size but not the quality of the video when downloading
the admin pages should recieve data from the users side so that it can show real data not mock or nil
create a review section that one can write reviews and view them in the landing page.
and the landing page is showing error and not showing that a user is logged in on that landing page, that means it logs out when i moves to the landing page
then on the dashboard create a watch history that  shows the the  movies i have watched as a list 
then  the subtitle when im downloading, it should show the name of the movie
then as a pro developer, scan all the files, look for all error  and bugs, remove the useless files 
then check this error Error loading dashboard: Cannot query field 'releaseYear' on type 'Movie'. Did you mean 'releaseDate'?
in the admin dashboard

work on the admin log, analysis, setting, report, genres, content, also make the logo on the admin side the samre with the one on the user dashboard. make the user page be able to see each user under view, where he can make admin, delete and some other things.
work on the notice on the admin page, 
create a page on the admin page where the admin can send notice to users  personal and collectively and it appears as a notice
also work on the chat, it is saving the chat and it is collapsing some thing in the website, also logging out user unnecessary




add family plan for 5 different account where an account invite other and do joint payment
next is Free / Standard / Pro tier enforcement
🔲 Subscription management page (upgrade, downgrade, cancel).
🔲 Payment history & receipts.
🔲 Failed payment handling & retry.
🔲 Refers 5 people and Upgrade tier to standard( as promo).
🔲 for the first subscription you have 1 month free 
🔲 CORS configuration.
🔲 Input sanitization.
🔲 JWT refresh token rotation.
🔲 Protect premium routes (middleware).
🔲 Service worker / PWA support.
🔲 Rate limiting on API routes.
🔲 Pagination or infinite scroll on movie lists.

i want to add pricing page ui  with its details below
Free Tier (0/month)
480p SD quality
1 screen at a time
5 downloads/month (7-day expiry, SD only)
Limited content library
Heavy ads (pre-roll, mid-roll, banners)
Basic watchlist (10 titles)
Watch history (last 30 days)
FAQ support only
Basic title search only

Standard (3k/month)
720p quality
15 downloads/month
Downloads expire after 14 days
Reduced ads
Full content library
watchlist (20 titles)
24/7 Community Chat
Email support


Pro (8k/month)
1080p + 4K quality
Unlimited downloads
AI-powered personalized recommendations
Zero ads
Family plan
Unlimited watchlist
Early access to new releases
Resume watching across devices
Priority email support
Watch history & yearly stats.
on the movie page when i select a filter, it does not work 





(FROM python:3.11-slim

ENV PYTHONUNBUFFERED=1 \
    PYTHONDONTWRITEBYTECODE=1 \
    PIP_NO_CACHE_DIR=1 \
    PIP_DISABLE_PIP_VERSION_CHECK=1 \
    PORT=8000

WORKDIR /app

# Install system dependencies
RUN apt-get update && apt-get install -y --no-install-recommends \
    build-essential \
    libpq-dev \
    && rm -rf /var/lib/apt/lists/*

# Install python dependencies
COPY requirements.txt .
RUN pip install -r requirements.txt

# Copy application source code
COPY . /app

# Expose the API port
EXPOSE 8000

# Start command
CMD ["uvicorn", "app.main:app", "--host", "0.0.0.0", "--port", "8000"]
)











📊 Admin Dashboard
👥 User Management

🔲 View all users & subscription status
🔲 Manually upgrade / downgrade / ban / delete accounts
🔲 Impersonate user (view site as them for debugging)
🔲 View user login history & active sessions
🔲 Force logout a user from all devices
🔲 Send direct message to a specific user
🔲 View user's watch history & activity
🔲 Manually verify email for a user
🔲 Reset a user's password from admin side
🔲 Flag / mark suspicious accounts


💰 Revenue & Subscriptions

🔲 Revenue overview (MRR, ARR, churn rate)
🔲 Total active subscribers per tier (Free / Standard / Pro)
🔲 Subscription growth chart (weekly / monthly)
🔲 Failed payments log & retry history
🔲 Refund management (approve / reject refund requests)
🔲 Coupon & promo code management (create, expire, track usage)
🔲 Referral tracking (who referred who, rewards given)
🔲 Family plan overview (which accounts are linked)
🔲 Revenue breakdown by payment method (card, bank, mobile money)
🔲 Export revenue report as CSV / PDF


🎬 Content Management

🔲 Add, edit, remove movies & series
🔲 Bulk upload movies via CSV
🔲 Assign content to tiers (Free only, Standard+, Pro only)
🔲 Schedule content release dates
🔲 Manage movie metadata (title, description, genre, cast, poster)
🔲 Upload & manage subtitles per movie
🔲 Manage multiple stream quality links per movie
🔲 Mark content as trending / featured / new release
🔲 Preview movie page as a user before publishing
🔲 Archive / unpublish content without deleting
🔲 View most watched, most bookmarked, highest rated movies


🔗 Stream & Link Management

🔲 View all stream links and their status (active / broken / expired)
🔲 Bulk validate all stream links at once
🔲 Replace broken stream links quickly
🔲 View reported broken streams from users
🔲 Monitor stream link expiry dates
🔲 CDN health status per link


💬 Chat & Community Moderation

🔲 View all active chat conversations
🔲 Delete / hide offensive messages
🔲 Ban users from chat
🔲 View reported messages & take action
🔲 Pin announcements in community chat
🔲 Mute specific users for a set duration
🔲 View chat activity logs


⭐ Reviews & Ratings Moderation

🔲 View all movie reviews
🔲 Delete / hide inappropriate reviews
🔲 View flagged / reported reviews
🔲 Ban users from posting reviews
🔲 Feature a review (pin to top)
🔲 View average rating history per movie


🔔 Notifications & Announcements

🔲 Send push notification to all users
🔲 Send notification to specific tier (e.g. Pro users only)
🔲 Schedule notification for a future date
🔲 Email blast to all users or segments
🔲 Create in-app announcement banners
🔲 View notification delivery & open rates


📈 Analytics & Reporting

🔲 Total watch time across platform
🔲 Peak usage hours heatmap
🔲 Most searched keywords
🔲 User retention rate (Day 1, Day 7, Day 30)
🔲 Conversion rate (Free → Standard → Pro)
🔲 Drop-off points during onboarding
🔲 Device breakdown (mobile, tablet, desktop)
🔲 Country / region breakdown of users
🔲 Ad revenue tracking (Free tier ads performance)
🔲 Export any report as CSV / PDF


🔒 Security & System

🔲 View all active sessions across the platform
🔲 Login attempt logs (failed logins, suspicious IPs)
🔲 IP blacklist management
🔲 API usage & rate limit logs
🔲 System health dashboard (server uptime, DB status, CDN)
🔲 Error logs viewer (without needing Sentry separately)
🔲 Audit log (who did what in the admin panel)
🔲 Admin role management (Super Admin, Moderator, Support)
🔲 Two-factor authentication for admin accounts


🎨 Site Configuration

🔲 Edit homepage banner / hero section without code
🔲 Manage featured movies carousel
🔲 Toggle maintenance mode on/off
🔲 Manage genre categories (add, rename, delete)
🔲 Configure ad placements for Free tier
🔲 Set download limits per tier from admin (no hardcoding)
🔲 Manage Terms of Service & Privacy Policy content
🔲 Configure referral reward rules
🔲 Set promo banner for special events (holidays, sales)
i want you to work on this 





next we will work on  forgot pasword and reset flow, session expiry and refresh token,  referral links, in the watch page, we work on next episode and season autoplay, the subtitle listshould have scroll. from the navbar remove series and anime with trending 
then in the filter in movies add the series and anime to the type.
work on loading skeleton, empty state ui

the watch and movies details page should have movie name as its url while on watch screen,
work on stream link obfusation(dont expose  raw url).
work on notifications(new releases, login), movie rating and review
then any film on this site that have episode or  season should be clasified under series and should have the series tag.




after 5 referral, the user upgrade for 2months free
 Sentry error logging, uptime monitoring config, and CI/CD pipeline:




 python -m app.core.migrate




Objective: Implement the following "V2" features across the ecosystem. Focus on deep-linking for mobile, background services for notifications, and robust RBAC (Role-Based Access Control) for the new Family Plan.

1. Social & Community Engagement
Share Functionality: Implement a "Share" button using the Native Share API on mobile and navigator.clipboard on web. Generate deep links (/movie/:id) that open the app directly.

Review Interactions: Add like and dislike toggles for user reviews. Include a "Report Review" flag that triggers a moderation alert in the backend.

Watch Party: Build a synchronized playback room.

Frontend: Use WebSockets (Socket.io) to sync play/pause/seek events across participants.

Mobile: Ensure low-latency state syncing and a "Join via Link" flow.

2. Retention & Communication (Notifications/Email)
Push Notifications: Integrate Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM). Set up triggers for "New Release," "Friend invited you to Watch Party," and "Subscription Renewal."

Email Ecosystem: * Gmail Integration: Ensure HTML emails are optimized for Gmail (using MJML or Tailwind-Email).

Weekly Digest: A cron-job triggered email summarizing "Top Picks for You" and "Continue Watching" progress.

Changelog & Discovery: * Onboarding Tour: Implement a tooltip library (like react-joyride) to walk new users through the UI.

"What's New": A modal popup that triggers once per version update to show new features.

3. Account & Subscription Logic (The Family Plan)
Independent Family Plan: Add a specific "Family" tier to the Pricing component.

Constraint: Hard-cap at 5 sub-accounts.

Invite System: The primary account holder can send "Invite Links" via email to join the plan.

UI Customization: Allow users to Rearrange the UI (e.g., drag-and-drop rows like "My List" to the top). Save this layout preference to the User_Settings table.

4. Accessibility & Quality of Life
ARIA & Standards: Audit all components for aria-label, keyboard navigation (Tab-index), and screen-reader compatibility.

Yearly Stats: Create a "Wrapped" style dashboard showing total minutes watched, top genres, and favorite actors for the year.

🛠 Technical Implementation Notes:
Pricing Strategy: In your database schema, ensure the FamilyPlan has a parent_id and member_slots (integer, max 5) to track sub-account allocations.

Background Tasks: Use BullMQ or Celery for the email digest and yearly stats generation to avoid slowing down the main API.

Deep Linking: Configure branch.io or standard Universal Links so "Share Movie" links transition smoothly from browser to mobile app.